# Mohammed Alghumayti

#### **PROFILE**

An ambitious leadership personality interested in the world of technology and everything that applies to it. A graduate of a network engineer and a database engineer who loves learning and continuous improvement in a specialized field.

# **INTERESTS**

Software Engineer | DevOps Engineer | System Administrator | Project Management

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Tech Product Manager & Development Lead** Lyrae Digital *⊗* 

01/2023 - present | Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

Software Engineer

01/2022 – 03/2022 Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

PureCode.sa

• Analyzed and described pros and cons of design, logical, and linguistic errors.

- · Collaborated on website planning and structure using ReactJS and components-based model.
- Demonstrated commitment to self-learning, improving skills in front-end programming, APIs, and AWS services.

# **EDUCATION**

King Abdulaziz University

2018 - 2023 | Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

Bachelor of Information Technology

Saudi Digital Academy

05/2022 - 09/2022 | Saudi Arabia

Diploma of Higher Education (DevOps Engineer)

- Linux, AWS, Bash & Python Scripting, Jenkins, Ansible, Docker, Kubernetes, Cloudformation, Terraform & More.
- Understand how various technologies work together in DevOps.

## **PROJECTS**

Babakom 05/2023 - present

Lyrae Digital

Babakom is a leading B2B marketplace in Saudi Arabia, revolutionizing business connections and trade (low code, type script).

Aims plus 2022

King Abdulaziz University

ABET-accredited Streamlined course management and coordination Automated processes that help advance database capabilities and empower coordinators for seamless modifications (ASP.NET MVC).

#### SKILLS

Innovation | Agility | Leadership | Communication Skills | Good speaker | Problem Solver

Creative Thinking | Team Work Player | Code structure & architecture | Data Analyst

Information Security | SIEM | BRD | System Requirements

# **AWARDS**

The challenge of augmented reality in education

12/03/2022

Saudi Electronic University

E-commerce hackathon 10/02/2022

Saudi Electronic University

10/01/2021

Saddi Licetionic oniversity

Savola Foods Hackathon "Shift Handover Automation"

SAVOLA Foods

### **LANGUAGES**